Guide to the Edmund Clarence Stedman Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Diaries
  - Keppler, Emil A.C. (Box 74)
  - Keppler, Rudolph (Box 74)
  - Kerr, C. Powell (Box 74)
  - Kerr, Charles H. (Box 74)
  - Kerr, John Bozman (Box 74)
  - Kersey, Ruth Morris (Box 74)
  - Keyes, Homer Eaton (Box 74)
  - Kiernan, Thomas J. (Box 74)
  - Kiliani, Lilian Bayard Taylor (Box 74)
  - Kimball, H. Ingalls, Jr. (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Hannah Parker (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Harriet M. (Box 74)
  - Kimball, H. Mc. (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Julia B (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Julia G (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Richard Burleigh (Box 74)
  - Kimball, Robert J. (Box 74)
  - Kinard, James Pickney (Box 75)
  - King, C.W. (Box 75)
  - King, Charles (Box 75)
  - King, Clarence (Box 75)
  - King, Clarence E. (Box 75)
  - King, Edward (Box 75)
  - King, Fred Alvin (Box 75)
  - King, Grace Elizabeth (Box 75)
  - King, Herbert Booth (Box 75)
  - King, Louise B. (Box 75)
  - King, Mary Perry (Box 75)
  - King, Morris Lee (Box 75)
  - King, Susan T. Bloode (Box 75)
  - King, W.G. (Box 75)
  - Kingsley, Rose (Box 75)
  - Kingsley, W.L. (Box 75)
  - Kinner, Charles R.C. (Box 75)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (Box 75)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (Box 76)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (1856-1866) (Box 77)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (1867-1873) (Box 78)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (1874-1878) (Box 79)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (1879-1888) (Box 80)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge. Manuscripts, A-I (Box 81)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge. Manuscripts, J-Pa (Box 82)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge. Manuscripts, Pe (Box 83)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge. Manuscripts, Ph-Pr (Box 84)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge. Manuscripts, Q-End (Box 85)
  - Kinney, Thomas Tallmadge (Box 86)
  - Kinney, William Burnet (Box 86)
  - Kinsella, James E. (Box 86)
  - Kip Elizabeth Clementine Kinney (Mrs. William) (Box 86)
  - Kip, Leonard (Box 86)
  - Kip, William Ingraham (Box 86)
  - Kip, William Ingraham, Jr. (Box 86)
  - Kirkland, Joseph (Box 86)
  - Kirkpatrick, Littleton (Box 86)
  - Kling, Flora Gardner (Box 86)
  - Kling, Anna D. (Box 86)
  - Klopsch, Louis (Box 86)
  - Knapp, Gilbert Peter (Box 86)
  - Knapp, Penelope Glesson (Box 86)
  - Knortz, Karl (Box 86)
  - Knott, Richard W. (Box 86)
  - Knowlton, Helen M. (Box 86)
  - Knox, Thomas Wallace (Box 86)
  - Koehler, Sylvester Rosa (Box 87)
  - Koopman, Harry Lyman (Box 87)
  - Korbay, F. (Box 87)
  - Kost, Henry C (Box 87)
  - Kelley, James P. (Box 87)
  - Kelly, William V. (Box 87)
  - Kellog, Miner Kilbourne (Box 87)
  - Kendall, May (Box 87)
  - Kennan, George (Box 87)
  - Kennedy, William Sloane (Box 87)
  - Kent, Henry Watson (Box 87)
  - Kent, William (Box 87)
  - Kenyon, Elvira (Box 87)
  - Kenyon, James Benjamin (Box 87)
  - Kenyon, W.C. (Box 87)
  - Keppel, Frederick (Box 87)
  - Keppler, Emil A.C. (Box 87)
  - Keppler, Rudolph (Box 87)
  - Kerr, C. Powell (Box 87)
  - Kerr, Charles H. (Box 87)
  - Kerr, John Bozman (Box 87)
  - Kersey, Ruth Morris (Box 87)
  - Keyes, Homer Eaton (Box 87)
  - Kiernan, Thomas J. (Box 87)
  - Kiliani, Lilian Bayard Taylor (Box 87)
  - Kimball, H. Ingalls, Jr. (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Hannah Parker (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Harriet M. (Box 87)
  - Kimball, H. Mc. (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Julia B (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Julia G (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Richard Burleigh (Box 87)
  - Kimball, Robert J. (Box 87)
  - Kinard, James Pickney (Box 87)
  - King, C.W. (Box 87)
  - King, Charles (Box 87)
  - King, Clarence (Box 87)
  - King, Clarence E. (Box 87)
  - King, Edward (Box 87)
  - King, Fred Alvin (Box 87)
  - King, Grace Elizabeth (Box 87)
  - King, Herbert Booth (Box 87)
  - King, Louise B. (Box 87)
  - King, Mary Perry (Box 87)
  - King, Morris Lee (Box 87)
  - King, Susan T. Bloode (Box 87)
  - King, W.G. (Box 87)
  - Kingsley, Rose (Box 87)
  - Kingsley, W.L. (Box 87)
  - Kinner, Charles R.C. (Box 87)
  - Kinney, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge (Box 87)
  - Kinney, Thomas Tallmadge (Box 87)
  - Kinney, William Burnet (Box 87)
  - Kinsella, James E. (Box 87)
  - Kip Elizabeth Clementine Kinney (Mrs. William) (Box 87)
  - Kip, Leonard (Box 87)
  - Kip, William Ingraham (Box 87)
  - Kip, William Ingraham, Jr. (Box 87)
  - Kirkland, Joseph (Box 87)
  - Kirkpatrick, Littleton (Box 87)
  - Kling, Flora Gardner (Box 87)
  - Kling, Anna D. (Box 87)
  - Klopsch, Louis (Box 87)
  - Knapp, Gilbert Peter (Box 87)
  - Knapp, Penelope Glesson (Box 87)
  - Knortz, Karl (Box 87)
  - Knott, Richard W. (Box 87)
  - Knowlton, Helen M. (Box 87)
  - Knox, Thomas Wallace (Box 87)
  - Koehler, Sylvester Rosa (Box 87)
  - Koopman, Harry Lyman (Box 87)
  - Korbay, F. (Box 87)
  - Kost, Henry C (Box 87)
  - Kraetzer, Adolph D. (Box 87)
  - Krehbiel, Henry Edward (Box 87)
  - Krueger, Frank (Box 87)
  - Kuhn, Arthur K. (Box 87)
  - Kuhns, Oscar (Box 87)
  - Kulp, Claire (Box 87)
  - Kunz, George Frederick (Box 87)
  - Kurtz, Charles M. (Box 87)
  - Kyle, Howard (Box 87)
  - Kyle, Louise (Box 87)
  - Lacey, Harry B. (Box 87)
  - The Ladies Home Journal (Box 87)
  - La Farge, John (Box 87)
  - Laffan, William Mackay (Box 87)
  - La Follette, Robert Marion (Box 87)
  - Laighton, Lucy D. (Box 87)
  - Lamb, H.F. (Box 87)
  - Lamb, Martha Joanna Read Nash (Box 87)
  - Lamborn, Charles (Box 87)
  - Lamborn, Emma S. Taylor (Box 87)
  - Lamborn, Robert Henry (Box 87)
  - Lancaster, Albert Edmund (Box 87)
  - Landon, Melville deLancey ("Eli Perkins") (Box 87)
  - Lane, Arnie Tichberg (Mrs. John) (Box 87)
  - Lane, Eben (Box 87)
  - Lane, John (Box 87)
  - Lang, Andrew (Box 88)
  - Langdon, W., Jr. (Box 88)
  - Lanier, Clifford (Box 88)
  - Lanier, D.G. (Box 88)
  - Lanier, Henry Wysham (Box 88)
  - Lanier, Mary Day (Mrs. Sidney) (Box 88)
  - Lanier, Sidney (Box 88)
  - Larham, J (Box 88)
  - Larremore, Wilbur (Box 88)
  - Latham, R.W. (Box 88)
  - Lathrop, Frances M. Smith (Box 89)
  - Lathrop, George Persons (Box 89)
  - Lathrop, Helen Marshall (Box 89)
  - Lathrop, Rose Hawthorne (Box 89)
  - Lathrop, Washington A. (Box 89)
  - Laughlin, Mary G. (Box 89)
  - Lawrence, Cyrus J. (Box 89)
  - Lavely, Henry Alexander (Box 89)
  - Lawrence, Isaac (Box 89)
  - Lawrence, Isaac (Box 89)
  - Lawrence, M. (Box 89)
  - Lawsing, E.S. (Box 89)
  - Lawton, William Cranston (Box 89)
  - Lazarus, Emma (Box 89)
  - Leakin, Marqaret (Box 90)
  - Learned, Ellen (Box 90)
  - Learned, James Edgerton (Box 90)
  - Learned, Walter (Box 90)
  - Lebkuecher, P. (Box 90)
  - Lee,.Albert (Box 90)
  - Lee, Albert (Box 90)
  - Lee, Benjamin (Box 90)
  - Lee, Emma Hale White (Mrs Benjamin) (Box 90)
  - Lee, John Thomas (Box 90)
  - Lee and Shepard (Box 90)
  - Lee-Hamilton, Eugene Jacob (Box 90)
  - Lefèvre, Edwin (Box 90)
  - Leffert, Henry (Box 90)
  - Le Galliene, Richard (Box 90)
  - Leggatt, ThoMas G. (Box 90)
  - Leigh, Oliver Herbrand Gordon (Box 90)
  - Leland, Carolyn Dennis (Box 90)
  - Leland, Eliza Bella Fisher (Box 90)
  - Leland, R.H. (Box 90)
  - Lemenager, Henri V. (Box 90)
  - LeMoyne, Sarah Cowell (Box 90)
  - Lemperly, Paul (Box 90)
  - Le Plongein, Augustus (Box 90)
  - Le Queux, William (Box 90)
  - Lesser, M.A. (Box 90)
  - LeVert, Octavia Walton (Mrs Henry) (Box 90)
  - Levy, Arthur (Box 90)
  - Lewis, Amanda K. (Box 90)
  - Lewis, Charles Bertrand (Box 90)
  - Lewis, Charlton Miner (Box 90)
  - Lewis, Charlton Thomas (Box 90)
  - Lewis, Juan (Box 90)
  - Libbey, Jonas Marsh (Box 91)
  - Libbie, F.J. (Box 91)
  - Lillie, Maria Elmendorf (Box 91)
  - Lincoln, L.J.B. (Box 91)
  - Lindley, John (Box 91)
  - Lindsey, William. (Box 91)
  - Lindsley, Mary J. (Box 91)
  - Linsley, John S (Box 91)
  - Linton, Nellie W. (Box 91)
  - Linton, William James (Box 91)
  - J.B. Lippincott Company (Box 91)
  - Lippincott, Martha Shepard (Box 91)
  - Lippman, Julie Mathilde (Box 91)
  - Litchfield, Fannie (Box 91)
  - Litchfield, Grace N (Box 91)
  - Little, Dorothy Q. (Box 91)
  - Little, J.J. & Co. (Box 91)
  - Little, James Stanley (Box 91)
  - Little, Joseph James (Box 91)
  - Little, Brown & Co. (Box 91)
  - Littlefield, George Emery (Box 91)
  - Lloyd, Alice C.W. (Box 92)
  - Lloyd, Beatrice Demarest (Box 92)
  - Lloyd, David Demarest (Box 93)
  - Lloyd, Eliza M. Shore (Box 93)
  - Lloyd, Henry Demarest (Box 93)
  - Lloyd, Malcolm (Box 93)
  - Lloyd, Sara (Box 93)
  - Lloyd, Storr H. (Box 93)
  - Locke, Charles F. (Box 93)
  - Lockwood, Ferris (Box 93)
  - Lodge, Anna Cabot Mills Davis (Box 93)
  - Lodge, George Cabot (Box 93)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 93)
  - Loeb, William (Box 93)
  - Loeber, Charles G. (Box 93)
  - Logan, James Parmelee (Box 93)
  - Lombard, Thomas C. (Box 93)
  - Long, Augustus White (Box 93)
  - Long, John D. (Box 93)
  - Long, John Luther (Box 93)
  - Longfellow, Alice M. (Box 93)
  - Lomis, Merion Lippincott (Box 93)
  - Lord, Margaret Stockton (Box 93)
  - Lord, William Sinclair (Box 93)
  - Long, William Wilberforce (Box 93)
  - Long, William Wilberforce, Jr. (Box 93)
  - Loring, Thomas L. (Box 93)
  - Lothrop Company (Box 93)
  - Loti, Pierre (Box 93)
  - Loughead, Flora Haines (Box 94)
  - Lounsbury, G. Constant (Box 94)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas (Box 94)
  - Lovejoy, Cooper Maxwell (Box 94)
  - Lovejoy, John (Box 94)
  - Loveman, Robert (Box 94)
  - Loveman, Samuel E. (Box 94)
  - Low, Seth (Box 94)
  - Low, Walter (Box 94)
  - Low, Will H. (Box 94)
  - Lowndes, Marie Adelaide Belloc (Box 94)
  - Lucas, Maud M. (Box 94)
  - Luce, Rear Admiral S.G. (Box 94)
  - Löders, Charles Henry (Box 94)
  - Löders, H. (Box 94)
  - Ludlow, Fitz-Hugh (Box 94)
  - Ludlow, James Meeker (Box 94)
  - Lukens, Henry Clay (Box 94)
  - Lumley, Arthur (Box 94)
  - Lusk, Anna H. (Box 94)
  - Lusk, William C. (Box 94)
  - Lusk, William T. (Box 94)
  - Luther, Martin (Box 94)
  - Lyman, Hart (Box 95)
  - Lugman, Mary Clementine Corey (Box 95)
  - Lyman, Stuart (Box 95)
  - Loos, E.M. (Box 95)
  - Mchie, Hamilton (Box 95)
  - McArdle, Edward (Box 95)
  - McCabe, William Gordon (Box 95)
  - McCaffey, C.O. (Box 95)
  - McCann, John Ernest (Box 95)
  - McCleary, James T. (Box 95)
  - McClellan, George Brinton (Box 95)
  - McClelland, Mary Greenway (Box 95)
  - McClure, Samuel Sidney (Box 95)
  - A.C. McClurg & Co. (Box 95)
  - MacColl, Norman (Box 95)
  - McCook, A. McD (Box 95)
  - McCormick, Alexander Agnew (Box 95)
  - McCormick, Eliot (Box 95)
  - McCrackan, W.D. (Box 95)
  - McCracken, Henry M. (Box 95)
  - McCrudden, Francis (Box 95)
  - MacCullock, Humber (Box 95)
  - McDavitt, Ina Lord (Box 96)
  - McDermott, Hugh Farrar (Box 96)
  - Macdonald, A.E. (Box 96)
  - MacDonald, Frances Charles (Box 96)
  - Macdonough, A. Rodney (Box 96)
  - McDowell, F.M. (Box 96)
  - McDowell, Henry Barden (Box 96)
  - MacDowell, Marian Nevins (Box 96)
  - McElheny, Belle (Box 96)
  - McElrath, Thomas (Box 96)
  - McElroy, John E. (Box 96)
  - McElroy, William H. (Box 96)
  - McEntee, Girard L. (Box 96)
  - McEntee, Jervis (Box 96)
  - McGaffey, Ernest (Box 96)
  - McGaffey, John (Box 96)
  - McGaffey, John (Box 96)
  - McGinnis, John, Jr. (Box 96)
  - McGraven (Box 96)
  - McGrew, B.H. (Box 96)
  - McIlhany, A.K. (Box 96)
  - McKay, David (Box 97)
  - McKay, Eric (Box 97)
  - Mackay, George D. (Box 97)
  - Mackaye, Percy Wallace (Box 97)
  - Mackaye, Robin W (Box 97)
  - Mckee, Thomas J. (Box 97)
  - MacKellar, Thomas (Box 97)
  - McKelway, St. Clair (Box 97)
  - McKinney, Mary Stuart (Box 97)
  - McLaws, Emily Lafayette (Box 97)
  - McLellan, J.A. (Box 97)
  - MacLeod, Elizabeth S. (Box 97)
  - MacManus, Seumas (Box 97)
  - McMaster, John Bach (Box 97)
  - MacMechan, Archibald (Box 97)
  - Macmillan, Frederick (Box 97)
  - Macmillan & Co. (Box 97)
  - Macon, John Alfred (Box 97)
  - McPherson, Logan Grant (Box 97)
  - McVickar, Catharine (Box 97)
  - Magill, Edward H. (Box 97)
  - Mahan, Captain Alfred Thayer (Box 97)
  - Mair, George MacDonald (Box 97)
  - Major, George M. (Box 97)
  - Malone, Walter (Box 97)
  - Manes, J.A. (Box 97)
  - Manly, Louise (Box 97)
  - Mann, William Dalton (Box 97)
  - Mansfield, Howard (Box 97)
  - Mansfield, Joseph King Fenno (Box 97)
  - Marble, A.P. (Box 98)
  - Marble, Manton (Box 98)
  - Marié, Josephine (Box 98)
  - Markham, Anna Catherine Murphy (Mrs EdWin) (Box 98)
  - Markham, Edwin (Box 98)
  - Markham, George D. (Box 98)
  - Marks, Lionel Simeon (Box 98)
  - Marquand, Henry (Box 98)
  - Marr, F.H. (Box 98)
  - Marsh, Ada Crisp (Box 98)
  - Marsh, Edward C1ark (Box 98)
  - Marshall, Helen (Box 98)
  - Marsland, Alice (Box 98)
  - Marston, Philip Bourke (Box 98)
  - Martin, Arthur Patchett (Box 98)
  - Marzials, Frank T. (Box 98)
  - Mason, Agnes Lee Carter (Box 99)
  - Mason, Caroline Atherton Briggs (Box 99)
  - Mason, Edward Tuckerman (Box 99)
  - Mason, Frank Holcomb (Box 99)
  - Massett, Stephen (Box 99)
  - Mather, Frank Jewett, Jr. (Box 99)
  - Mather, Margaret Morgan Herbert (Box 99)
  - Mathews, Albert (Box 99)
  - Matthews, Agnes R (Box 99)
  - Matthews, J. Brander (Box 99)
  - Maynard, George Willoughby (Box 99)
  - Mayo, William Starbuck (Box 99)
  - Mead, Leon (Box 100)
  - Mead, William Rutherford (Box 100)
  - Meigs, Montgomery Cunningham (Box 100)
  - Melliss, David M (Box 100)
  - Meltzer, Charles Henry (Box 100)
  - Melville, Elizabeth Shaw (Box 100)
  - Melville, Herman (Box 100)
  - Mercier, Alfred (Box 100)
  - Meredith, William (Box 100)
  - Merington, Marguerite (Box 100)
  - Merrill, Charles E., Jr (Box 100)
  - Merrill, William Henry (Box 100)
  - Metcalf, Henry Aiken (Box 100)
  - Metcalf, Lorettus Sutton (Box 100)
  - Methuen, (Sir) Algernon Methuen Marshall (Box 100)
  - Meyers, Robert Carroll Vyvyan (Box 100)
  - Middagh, Belle (Box 100)
  - Mielaz, Charles F (Box 100)
  - Mifflin, George H (Box 100)
  - Mifflin, Lloyd (Box 100)
  - Milburn, William Henry (Box 101)
  - Miles, G.E. (Box 101)
  - Miller, Charles A. (Box 101)
  - Miller, Charles Ransom (Box 101)
  - Miller,.DeWitt (Box 101)
  - Miller, Harriet Mann (Box 101)
  - Miller, J. Warren (Box 101)
  - Miller; Joaquin (Box 101)
  - Miller, Juanita (Box 101)
  - Miller, Katherine (Box 101)
  - Miller,.Paul W. (Box 101)
  - Miller, Renette C. (Box 101)
  - Miller, Tillie E. (Box 101)
  - Milligan, Sam (Box 101)
  - Millman, William L’Estrange (Box 101)
  - Mills, Mariette Benedict Thompson (Box 101)
  - Miner, George Roberts (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Edward Page (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Ellen M (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Langdon Elwyn (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Silas Weir (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Walter (Box 101)
  - Moffett, Mary E. Lusk (Box 102)
  - Moffett, Samuel E (Box 102)
  - Monahan, Michael (Box 102)
  - Monell, Caroline Elizabeth DeWint (Box 102)
  - Monkhouse, Emilie H. (Box 102)
  - Monroe, Harriet (Box 102)
  - Monroe, Lucy (Box 102)
  - Monroe, Will Seymour (Box 102)
  - Montfort, Thomas Pierce (Box 103)
  - Montgomery, Antoinette Wood (Box 103)
  - Montgomery, George Edgar (Box 103)
  - Montgomery, Mary C. (Box 103)
  - Montgomery, Thomas Harrison (Box 103)
  - Monti, Fanny A. (Box 103)
  - Moody, Helen (Box 103)
  - Moody, William Vaughn (Box 103)
  - Moody, Winfield Scott (Box 103)
  - Moore, Charles Leonard (Box 103)
  - Moore, George Henry (Box 103)
  - Moore, Hannah Augusta (Box 103)
  - Moore, Jacob B. (Box 103)
  - Moore, L. Bruce (Box 103)
  - Moorehead., F.G. (Box 103)
  - Moran, John (Box 103)
  - Morgan, Forrest (Box 103)
  - Morgan, James Appleton (Box 103)
  - Morgan, John Pierpont, Jr. (Box 103)
  - Morgridge, Harriet Sampson (Box 103)
  - Morrell, Elizabeth (Box 103)
  - Morris, George P. (Box 103)
  - Morris, Gould (Box 103)
  - Morris, Harrison S. (Box 104)
  - Morris, Ramsay (Box 105)
  - Morris, Stuyvesant F. (Box 105)
  - Morrison, George H (Box 105)
  - Morrison, Mary Whitney (Box 105)
  - Morse, Edwin Wilson (Box 105)
  - Morse, George R (Box 105)
  - Morse, James Herbert (Box 105)
  - Morse, William H. (Box 105)
  - Mortara, J. de (Contessa) (Box 105)
  - Morton, A.H. (Box 105)
  - Morton, Levi Parsons (Box 105)
  - Mosher, Thomas Bird (Box 106)
  - Moss, Fanny B.G. (Box 106)
  - Moulton, Charles Wells (Box 106)
  - Moulton, Louise Chandler (Box 106)
  - Muldane, Elizabeth H. (Box 107)
  - Munby, Arthur Joseph (Box 107)
  - Munger, Theodore Thornton (Box 107)
  - Munkittrick, Richard Kendall (Box 107)
  - Munn, George Frederick (Box 107)
  - Munroe, David Alexander (Box 107)
  - Munson, Samuel Lyman (Box 107)
  - Munsterberg, Hugo (Box 107)
  - Murphey, Katharine E. (Box 107)
  - Murphe, Mrs. Arthur (Box 107)
  - Murphy, James S. (Box 107)
  - Murphy, Katherine Crosby (Box 107)
  - Murray, Ada M. Nealy (Box 107)
  - Murray, William Henry Harrison (Box 107)
  - Myer, Issac (Box 107)
  - Mylene, Alice H. (Box 107)
  - Nash, Jessie Bryan (Box 107)
  - Nason, Emma Huntington (Box 107)
  - Nevin, Ethelbert [Woodbridge] (Box 107)
  - Newbould, Thomas M (Box 107)
  - Newcomb, Simon (Box 107)
  - Newel, Sophie (Box 107)
  - Newell, Cordelia Stansbury (Box 107)
  - Newell, Robert Henry (Box 107)
  - Nichols, Mrs. Kate Lee (Box 107)
  - Nichols, Starr Hoyt (Box 107)
  - Nicholson, D. (Box 107)
  - Nicholson, Paul L (Box 107)
  - Nicoll, James Craig (Box 107)
  - Noble, Charles (Box 107)
  - Noble, Lucretia Gray (Box 107)
  - Noguchi, Yone (Box 107)
  - Nordstrom, Charels E (Box 107)
  - Norris, Evelyn L.I. (Box 107)
  - Norris, Jessie (Box 107)
  - Norris, Seymor (Box 107)
  - Northrop H.R. (Box 107)
  - Northrop, Cyrus (Box 107)
  - Northrup, Ansel Judd (Box 107)
  - Northrup, E.D. (Box 107)
  - Norton, Charles Eliot (Box 107)
  - Norton, Charles Ledyard (Box 107)
  - Norton, Dora Miriam (Box 107)
  - Norton, H.B. (Box 107)
  - Noyes, Kate Adéle (Box 107)
  - Nye, Edgar Wilson (Box 107)
  - Oakes, T.F. (Box 108)
  - Oakley, Violet (Box 108)
  - Obrig, Adolph (Box 108)
  - O’Byrne. George (Box 108)
  - O'Connor, Ellen M. Tarr (Box 108)
  - O’Connor, Joseph (Box 108)
  - O’Connor, William Douglas (Box 108)
  - O’Donnell, M.S. (Box 108)
  - O’Donovan, William Rudolph (Box 108)
  - O'Reilly, John Boyle (Box 108)
  - Older, Cora Miranda Baggerly (Box 108)
  - Oldham, Edward A. (Box 108)
  - Oldroyd, O.H. (Box 108)
  - Olds, Deborah Ege (Box 108)
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law (Box 108)
  - Osborne, Duffield (Box 108)
  - Osborne, J. (Box 108)
  - Osborne, Marcus B. (Box 108)
  - Osgood, James Ripley (Box 108)
  - Osgood, Kate Putnam (Box 108)
  - Pacchiotti, Dr. Giancinto (Box 109)
  - Packard, Charlotte Mellen (Box 109)
  - Page, Benjamin Price (Box 109)
  - Page, Curtis Hidden (Box 109)
  - Page, Fred M (Box 109)
  - Page, Halter Hines (Box 109)
  - Page, Thomas Nelson (Box 109)
  - Paget, R. Harold (Box 109)
  - Paine, Albert Bigelow (Box 109)
  - Paine, Henry Gallup (Box 109)
  - Paine, John Knowles (Box 109)
  - Paine, John Williamson (Box 109)
  - Palmer, Francis Sterne (Box 109)
  - Palmer, Frank (Box 109)
  - Palmer, Mary (Box 109)
  - Paret, Henry (Box 110)
  - Park, Pub. Co. (Box 110)
  - Parker, Benjamin S (Box 110)
  - Parker, Henry G (Box 110)
  - Parker, Sir Gilbert Niles, Thomas (Box 110)
  - Parker, Theodore (Box 110)
  - Parry-Evans, J. (Box 110)
  - Parsons, Charles (Box 110)
  - Parsons, Eugene (Box 110)
  - Parsons, George Frederic (Box 110)
  - Parsons, J.H. (Box 110)
  - Parsons, Thomas William (Box 110)
  - Partlan, Anne (Box 110)
  - Parton, Ellen W. Edredge (Mrs James) (Box 110)
  - Partridge, William Ordway (Box 110)
  - Pattee, Fred Lewis (Box 110)
  - Patterson, Samuel D (Box 110)
  - Paul, C. Kegan & Co. (Box 111)
  - Paul, Dr. J. Marshall (Box 111)
  - Paul., James W. (Box 111)
  - Payne, William Norton (Box 111)
  - Peabody, Josephine (Box 111)
  - Peacock, Gibson (Box 111)
  - Peacock, Thomas Brower (Box 111)
  - Peacock, Walter F. (Box 111)
  - Pearson, A.W. (Box 111)
  - Pearson, J.C. (Box 111)
  - Peck, Harry Thurston (Box 111)
  - Peck, Samuel Minturn (Box 111)
  - Peckham, George (Box 111)
  - Pierce, Charles Sauders (Box 112)
  - Peixotto, .George D.M. (Box 112)
  - Pellew, Charles E. (Box 112)
  - Pendleton, Francis Key (Box 112)
  - Pendleton, Louis (Box 112)
  - Pennell, Elizabeth Robins (Box 112)
  - Pennock, Frederick M. (Box 112)
  - Pennypacker, Isaac Rusling (Box 112)
  - Pepper, George Wharton (Box 112)
  - Pepper, Henry (Box 112)
  - Perkins, Frederick Beecher (Box 112)
  - Perkins, James Breck (Box 112)
  - Perkins, H.L.W. (Box 112)
  - Perkins, R.G. (Box 112)
  - Perkins, William R. (Box 112)
  - Perrin, Raymond St. James (Box 112)
  - Perry, Bliss (Box 112)
  - Perry, George (Box 112)
  - Perry, Nora (Box 112)
  - Perry, P.A. (Box 112)
  - Peters, Madison C. (Box 112)
  - Peterson, Arthur (Box 112)
  - Peterson, Frederick (Box 112)
  - Peterson, Henry (Box 112)
  - Peterson, Maud Howard (Box 112)
  - T.B. Peterson & Brothers (Box 112)
  - Pfeiffer, J. Edward (Box 113)
  - Phelps, Charles Henry (Box 113)
  - Phelps, Mary Booth (Box 113)
  - Phelps, William Walter (Box 113)
  - Phillips, C.F. (Box 113)
  - Philip, Franklin (Box 113)
  - Platt, John James (Box 114)
  - Pickard, Samuel Thomas (Box 115)
  - Piedra, Alice Brender (Mrs Pedro) (Box 115)
  - Pierce, George Winslow (Box 115)
  - Pilch, Frederick Henry (Box 115)
  - Pilling, James Constantine (Box 115)
  - Pinchot, Gifford (Box 115)
  - Pinède, L.A.R. (Box 115)
  - Pinker, James B (Box 115)
  - Pinneo, Mrs. E.S. (Box 115)
  - Pinney, L.V. (Box 115)
  - Pitman, Marie J. (Box 115)
  - Platt, Belle H. (Box 116)
  - Platt, Charles B (Box 116)
  - Platt, Thomas Collier (Box 116)
  - Plunkett, Mrs. H.M. (Box 116)
  - Poe, Amelia F (Box 116)
  - Poe, Edgar Allan (Box 116)
  - Polhaminus &.Jackson (Box 116)
  - Polk, Anne B., Lamborn (Box 116)
  - Polk, Frank H (Box 116)
  - Pollok, Anthony (Box 116)
  - Pomeroy, Samuel Clarke (Box 116)
  - Pond, James Burton (Box 116)
  - Pontz, E.L. (Box 116)
  - Poore, Benjamin Perley (Box 116)
  - Porter, A.D. (Box 116)
  - Porter, Charlotte E (Box 116)
  - Porter, Fitz-John (Box 116)
  - Porter, H.H. (Box 116)
  - Porter, Henry Alfred (Box 116)
  - Porter, Henry Chester (Box 116)
  - Porter, John Stuart (Box 116)
  - Porter, Lucille Sayre (Mrs Henry A.) (Box 116)
  - Porter, Mary Louise Tucker (Mrs John S) (Box 116)
  - Porter, Noah (Box 116)
  - Porter, Susan S. (Dodge) (Box 116)
  - Post, Sugustus (Box 117)
  - Potter, Julian (Box 117)
  - Pouillet, Eugene (Box 117)
  - Powell, C. Leslie (Box 117)
  - Powell, Lyman Pierson (Box 117)
  - Powers, Hiram. (Box 117)
  - Powers, Horatio Nelson (Box 117)
  - Powers, Lorelie (Box 117)
  - Pratt, Anna Meria (Box 117)
  - Pratt, Charles Stuart (Box 117)
  - Pratt, Ellan Farman (Box 117)
  - Pratt, L.C. (Box 117)
  - Prentiss, Marjorie L. (Box 117)
  - Preston, George (Box 117)
  - Price, Thomas Randolph (Box 117)
  - Prime, Mary R (Box 118)
  - Prime, Samuel I (Box 118)
  - Prime, Wendell (Box 118)
  - Proctor, Edna Dean (Box 119)
  - Proudfit, David Law (Box 119)
  - Pryor, Roger Atkinson (Box 119)
  - Pryor, Sara Agnes Rice (Box 119)
  - Pulitzer, Walter (Box 119)
  - Pullen, Elizabeth S. Jones Cavazza (Box 119)
  - Pullen, Eugene Henry (Box 119)
  - Pullen, Stanley T. (Box 119)
  - Pusey, Henry (Box 120)
  - Putnam, George Haven (Box 120)
  - Putnam, George Palmer (Box 120)
  - Putnam, Herbert (Box 120)
  - Putnam, Irving (Box 120)
  - Putnam, John Bishop (Box 120)
  - Putnam, Sallie Brock (Box 120)
  - Pyle, Howard (Box 120)
  - Pyle, Mary W (Box 120)
  - Pyle, Walter Lytle (Box 120)
  - Quicksilver Mining Co. (Box 120)
  - Quigley Co. (Box 120)
  - Quimby, Mary (Box 120)
  - Radford, Ernest (Box 121)
  - Radford, Ernest (Box 121)
  - Ramos Gonzales, Francisco (Box 121)
  - Ransay, Gilbert (Box 121)
  - Ramsey, N.A. (Box 121)
  - Rand, Theodore H. (Box 121)
  - Randall, James Ryder (Box 121)
  - Randolph, Arthur D.F. (Box 121)
  - Rankin, Henry Hilliam (Box 121)
  - Ranous, Dora Knowlton (Box 121)
  - Ransom, William S. (Box 121)
  - Ransom, L.J. (Box 121)